The clock is ticking for the human race…
Abduction is a horror, science fiction, thriller
film directed by Ernie Barbarash.
A man steps out of a park fountain in Ho Chi Minh City with no
recollection of who he is or where he came from.
As he wanders through the city, piecing together clues to his past,
he is relentlessly pursued by mysterious figures.
Quinn, played by Scott Adkins.
Conner, played by Andy On Chi-Kit.
Maya, played by Lily Ji.
Dao, played by Aki Aleong.
Anna, played by Trương Ngọc Ánh.
The Visitor, played by Daniel Whyte.
Abduction is a 2011 American action thriller film directed by John Singleton (in his final directed film before
his death in 2019), produced by Roy Lee and Ellen Goldsmith-Vein, and written by Shawn Christensen.
The film stars Taylor Lautner in the lead role, alongside Lily Collins, Alfred Molina,
Jason Isaacs, Maria Bello, and Sigourney Weaver in supporting roles.
The film follows a young man who sets out to uncover the truth about his life
after finding his child photo on a missing-person's website.
The film, Singleton's last before his death in 2019, was
released by Lionsgate on September 23, 2011.
The film received negative reviews.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking and intense.